garyjohnson2016.com 2016-11-18

# Privacy Policy & Terms of Use - Gary Johnson for President

#### (Updated 8/2016)

At Gary Johnson 2016 we are committed to protecting your privacy online.

Our privacy policy explains the information practices we use at the Gary Johnson 2016 website related to: How we protect your information.

How we use your information. How to contact us about privacy.

Our site links to a limited number of other websites. Gary Johnson 2016 is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of these websites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements for each website you visit. Gary Johnson 2016 will occasionally update this privacy policy as changes to the site necessitate it. When Gary Johnson 2016 posts changes to this policy, you will see the word “updated” next to the privacy policy link on the front page of this website. We encourage you to periodically review this policy to be informed of how we are protecting your information.

**How do we protect your information?**

Our website has a number of security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of certain sensitive information under our control. Computer systems have restricted access limited only to those persons and organizations necessary to its proper functioning. This access applies to all electronic and physical security measures. Highly sensitive data including credit card information is additionally secured through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software. Our servers are located in a locked, secure environment.

However, the security of information and payments transmitted via the internet cannot be guaranteed. We are not responsible for the operation of any security features, and are not liable for any loss you may suffer if a third party obtains unauthorized access to any information you provide, unless we are grossly negligent.

**How do we use the information you provide?**

On registration, sign-up and contribution forms on Gary Johnson 2016, we may ask for your name, address, telephone number, credit card information, bank account information, email address and/or IM address as well as the name of the person who referred you to the site or other information. We may also obtain information about you from outside sources and add it to or combine it with the information we collect through this site. By using our website and providing your information, you consent to our use, storage, and reporting of such information for any lawful purpose including without limitation:

Federal law requires us to use our best efforts to collect and report the name, mailing address, occupation, and name of the employer of each individual whose aggregate contributions exceed $200 in an election cycle or calendar year, as applicable. These records are available to the public. We also make a note of your telephone number and email address, which helps us to contact you quickly if follow-up on your contribution is necessary under federal law and communicate with you in the future.

Information may be used to process requests, credit those who are organizing volunteer support or fundraising for Gary Johnson 2016, provide you with news and information about us, including via text messaging. We may also use your zip code and state to send you email messages about upcoming events or activities in your area.

When you sign petitions, we treat your name, city, state, and any comments as public information. We may, for example, provide compilations of petitions, with your comments, to national leaders. We may also make comments along with your city and state available to the press and public online.

**Third Party Social-Networking and User-Generated Content Websites:**

Gary Johnson 2016 has established and maintains profiles and pages on several third-party social-networking and user-generated content websites. Gary Johnson 2016 is not responsible for the content of individual users or the privacy policies of these websites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements for each of these websites website you join. Gary Johnson 2016 may contact you via these websites using any contact methods that exist on the website and are within the website’s terms of service agreement. Gary Johnson 2016 reserves the right to republish any content that you publicly post or share on our social-networking and user-generated profiles/pages without compensation to you for use on our website or in any other communications or advertisements and for use with other individuals or entities, including other internet users, as well print or broadcast news media to use such material in their communications.

**Cookies:**

A cookie is a tiny text file that is stored on your computer by Gary Johnson 2016. We use cookies to tailor your experience on our site according to the preferences you have specified. When you visit the Gary Johnson 2016 website we only access the cookie file that we have stored on your computer. We cannot and do not access any information stored in a cookie by other websites. Our cookies do not contain any personal identifiable information.

We log the IP address, which is the location of your computer or network on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. We also use page hits in the aggregate to track the popularity of pages that people visit in order to improve the quality of the site. There is no personal identifiable information collected in our log files.

**Information on Children:**

Because we care about the safety and privacy of children online, we comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). COPPA and its accompanying FTC regulations establish United States federal law that protects the privacy of children using the Internet. We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. Our site is not intended to solicit information of any kind from children under 13, and we have designed our sites to block our knowing acceptance of information from children under 13 whenever age-related information is requested. Parents with questions may email us at [info@JohnsonWeld.com ](mailto:info@JohnsonWeld.com)

**How can you contact us?**

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, the information we have collected from you online, the practices of this site or your interaction with this website, send email to: [info@JohnsonWeld.com ](mailto:info@JohnsonWeld.com)

**Refund Policy:**

Gary Johnson 2016 thanks you for your generous support and donations. Because we create our campaign plans based off of the donations we receive we do not offer any refunds for the donations received. Once again, we thank you for your support.
